daniellelaporte.com 2018-11-28

# Privacy Policy • Danielle LaPorte: white hot truth + sermons on life

### DANIELLELAPORTE.COM

Effective Date: 25 May 2018 

The following Privacy Policy governs the online information collection practices of DANIELLE LAPORTE, INC. “COMPANY,”we” or “us”). Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather about you while you are using the daniellelaporte.com website (the “Site”), and the ways in which we use this information. This Privacy Policy, including our children’s privacy statement, does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means (for example, at a live event, via telephone, or through the mail) insofar as the collected private data does not form a part of a filing system.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting and using the Site, you agree that your use of our Site, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy. Because the Web is an evolving medium, we may need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, in which case we’ll post the changes to this Privacy Policy on this website and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use the Site after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified.

Daniellelaporte.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. “Period.”

* * *

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. We shall always ask you to provide only a minimum data which is needed for completing the service you asked for. Before leaving your data you will be clearly and intelligibly explained the purpose of collecting your data and asked to give your consent to it, which you can also withdraw easily. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

* * *

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To personalize your experience, to improve our website, to improve customer service, to process transactions, administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature and to send periodic emails.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

* * *

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we are required to comply by law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

* * *

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

* * *

## Records of processing activities

We shall maintain the Records of processing activities which shall include, inter alia, the list of all processing activities, purposes of processing, categories of personal data processed and subjects of those data, etc. what means that we shall take due care of every your input providing us with your personal information, such as name, e-mail, address, card number and alike.

* * *

## Your rights

You have the right to withdraw your consent on providing us your personal data, at any time, and to ask us to erase your data.

You may ask to see your data that you gave to us, and thus to exercise your right to access data.

If it happens that data you gave us is incorrect from any reason, you may ask for rectification of your data.

You also have the right to ask for restriction of access to your data, in which case the data shall not be erased, but just access thereto shall be denied.

Where you consented to give us data, or we process your data on the grounds of contract with you, if the processing is carried out by automated means, you may request that we send your data back in a structured way, and thus exercise your right to data portability.

* * *

## Whom you may address to?

For any privacy issue that you are having with your data that you entrusted to us, regarding your rights as written above, we have opened an e-mail through which you may address us, and we shall come to you quickly.

* * *

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. However, if you still do not want us to place cookies to your computers, you may set your browser not to accept cookies.

* * *

## Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

This children’s privacy statement explains our practices with respect to the online collection and use of personal information from children under the age of thirteen for non-EU users and under the age of sixteen for EU-users, and provides important information regarding their rights under federal law with respect to such information.

This Site is not directed to children under the age of thirteen for non-EU users, nor to children under the age of sixteen for EU-users, and we do NOT knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the said age limits as part of the Site. We screen users who wish to provide personal information in order to prevent users under the age of thirteen and sixteen respectively from providing such information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from an underage user as part of the Site, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen for non-EU users or sixteen for EU users as part of the Site.

Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from underage children as part of the Site, we also do NOT knowingly distribute such information to third parties.

We do NOT knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen for non-EU users or sixteen for EU users to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through the Site.

Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen for non-EU users or under the age of sixteen for EU users as part of the Site, we do NOT condition the participation of such children in the Site’s online activities on providing personally identifiable information.

* * *

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline, insofar it does not relate to filling offline systems.

**Changes to this Policy**

COMPANY reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

**Governing law**

This policy and the use of these Sites are governed by laws of Vancouver, B.C. Canada. THE COMPANY adheres to principles of the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) and General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) wishing to provide all its customers with the highest standards in privacy protection. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Canada. 

Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

DanielleLaPorte.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely in Vancouver, B.C. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

* * *

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us at support@daniellelaporte.com.

Danielle LaPorte Inc.  
Suite #234 – 2055 Commercial Drive  
Vancouver BC, V5N 0C7
